Slot3: (According to Slot1.txt)

III. SOLUTION and PROJECT
1. PROJECT: A PROJECT WILL CONSIT/HAVE MUILTIPLE SOURCE CODE FILES (.CS)
		TO SOLVE A. SPECIFIC THING, E.G

		A PROJECT IS CREATE TO OFFER/WORK WITH THE DATABASE ACTIVITIES
				LIKE CRUD - CREATE/RETRIEVE-READ/UPDATE/DELETE

		A PROJECT IS RESPONSIBILITY FOR SHOWING THE UI/DATA TO THE END-USER

		A PROJECT IS DESIGNED TO MANAGE AUTHENTICATION ACTIVITIES

		A PROJECT IS DEVELOPED TO MANAGE ALL PAYMENT ACTIVITIES 

** EACH PROJECT IS DESIGN TO DO A SPECIFIC TASK
	“”DIVIDE  & CONQUER” -> EASY TO MANAGE DEVELOMENT TEAM/DEVELOPMENT TASK
							        FOR	 MAINTERNANCE ACTIVITIES

2. SOLUTION: IS THE ANSWER TO THJE END-USER
		        IS AN APPLICATION THAT WE OFFER TO THE MARKET, TO THE END-USER
			CONSITS OF 
			CONTAINS OF MULTIPLE PROJECTS

EX:  		FIFA GAME
		
		LEAGUE OF LEGENDS - APP/SOFTWARE (PLAYER VIEW)            SOUITION (DEV VIEW)	  	 					- exe file				                                   AUTHENTICATION PROJECT
							- dll					                           TRADING MARKET PROJECT
		 					- dll					                           ADMIN PROJECT
							- dll					                           ROUND-1/LEVEL-1 PROJECT

3. A SOLUTION WILL HAVE MULTIPLE PROJECTS
    A PROJECT WILL PRODUCE A .DLL FILE
    A .DLL WILL HAVE MULTIPLE .CS FILES INSIDE (USE DOTPEEK TO CHECK)
    A PROJECT WILL HAVE MULTIPLE NAMESPACES
    A NAMESPACE WILL HAVE MULTIPLE CLASSES
    A CLASS WILL HAVE MULTIPLE METHODS/FUNCTIONS
  
4. NAMESPACE (JAVA PACKAGE)
- A TECHNIQUE TO GROUP/CLASSIFY THE RELATIVE CLASSES
			  WE DIVIDE/CATEGORIZE ALL RELATIVE CLASSED INTO A GROUP, GIVE EACH GROUP 
			  A NAME. THIS NAME/THE NAME OF EACH GROUP OF CLASSES IS SO CALLED NAMESPACE

- A NAMESPACE IS THE NAME OF A GROUP OF CLASSES - ĐẶT TÊN GỌI CHO 1 NHÓM CLASS (NAME FOR A GROUP OF CLASSES)

** BENEFIT TO USE NAMESPACE: TO AVOID THE NAME COLLISSION BETWEEN MULTIPLE CLASS
				2 CLASSES IN A PROJECT CAN HAVE THE SAME NAME, BUT IN DIFFERENT NAMESPACE
					
** BY DEFAULT, THE NAME OF PROJECT THE ROOT FOLDER OF PROJECT IS  USED TO NAME THE NAMESPACE					 							
III. CODING CONVENTION - YOU MUST FOLLOW OR YOU WILL GET A FIND/“A CHECK VAR”
1. THE SOLUTION NAME AND PROJECT NAME
- NOUN
- …

2. THE NAMESPACE NAME (PACKAGE NAME IN JAVA)
- NOUN 
- JAVA: com.mycompany.myproject.mymodule;  	import com.mycompany.     ;
	    com.microsoft.sqlserver.jdbc
	    LOWER CASE 
- C#:  (Pascal Case Notation with . and in the natural order)
	 Microsoft.SqlServer.AdoNet…
	 Bmi
	 FU.Bmi

3. THE CLASS NAME
- NOUN STANDS FOR A TYPE, A CATEGORY. A CLASSIFICATION
- Pascal Case Notation, a multiple words, each 1st  letter of each word is UPPERCASE
	ex: Bmi, BMI, BmiCalculator, Repository. DataAccessLayer

4. THE METHOD NAME
- VERB + OBJECT
- Pascal Case Notation (but in Java, camel Case Notation)
		C#						Java
	ex: GetBmi() 					getBmi() 
	      Main() 					main()

5. THE VARIABLE NAME
- For the local variable, (the var. is declared inside a method/function)
- NOUN
- camel Case Notation ()


			