Slot 7:
V. OOP - OBJECT ORIENTED PARADIGM (MINDSET - THE WAY WE THINK)
									PROGRAMMING (AN APPROACH - 1 CÁCH TIẾP CẬN)

WE WORK WITH OBJECTS, WE DEFINE OBJECTS DURING THE PROGRAMMING PROCESS
WHAT IS AN. OBJECT???

1. BEFORE OOP IS.. PROCEDUAL PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE (C, PASCAL)
- PROCEDURAL/PROCEDURE: STEPS, A SET OF STEPS TO DO SOMETHING(THỦ TỤC, TRÌNH TỰ CÁC BƯỚC)
- C, PASCAL, TO PROCESS SOMETHING, WE DEFINE FUNCTIONS AND VARIABLES, BUT IN A FREE WAY

#include <lib to be used in code>
#include <stdio.h>

//define variables - store the value before/after processing
//global variables
int yob;

//define functions - to process global vars, and local vars
int getAge() {
	return 2024 - yob;	
}

int main() {
	to call the functions()
}
//PROBLEMS:
//MULTIPLE FUNCTIONS CAN PLAY WITH THE SHARED VARIABLES - GLOBAL VARIABLES
//SIDE EFFECT(TÁC DỤNG PHỤ, HIỆU ỨNG LỀ) - WE CAN NOT CONTROL THE VALUE OF GLOBAL VARIABLE IN A STRICTLY WAY
//SINCE THERE ARE MULTIPLE METHODS/FUNCTIONS CAN CHANGE IT

2. OOP COMES TO SOLVE..
Every thing, THING around us comes with two different forms, can be described in two different forms
Sự vật quanh ta thể hiện qua 2 hình thức (form)
*1st form: a single value
*2nd form: a complex value

*1st form: a single value, e.g: 3.14; 9.8(gravity) 
								   300.000 km/s (speed of a light),
								   8-10% (VAT: value added tax),
								   50 km/h (speed of your motor),
								   5 (passed grade)
	single value: it is only a value, stands some thing, and itself has a meaning, do not need some extra effort to explain

* 2nd form - complex value - we can describe about it (THING) by its character, by its attributes, by using the other single values
	EX: Messi - FullName : Leonardo..
		 		   DOB	        :	_______
				   Homeland: Argentina
				   Club		   : _______  
				   Awards	   : _______
				   Number	   : 	    10
				   Goals	   : _______
						…………..

		  Car Honda City 2023	
					Model		 : _______
					Manu Date: _______
					Gas/km	 : _______
					Price		 : _______
					Settings	 : _______

- COMPLEX VALUE WE CALL IT AS AN OBJECT
  AN OBJECT IS A THING AROUND US THAT HAS ITS OWN ATTRIBUTES, PROPERTIES

——————————————————————————————————————————

WHAT HAPPEND IF WE HAVE MANY OBJECTS, HOW TO MANAGE MANU OBJECTS IN A EFFECTIVE WAY
- car1(…), car2(…), dog1(…), dog2(…), phone1(…), phone2(…), person1(…), person2(…)

CLASSIFY (VERB), GROUP, CATEGORIZE OBJECTS INTO APPROPRIATE GROUP, APPROPRIATE CLASS BASED ON THE COMMON SHARE BETWEEN THEM

CLASS: THE NAME OF EACH OF GROUP, WHERE ALL OF THINS BELONG TO THAT CLASS SHARE THE SAME ATTRIBUTE/PROPERTIES
CLASS: LÀ TÊN GỌI CỦA NHÓM OBJECT MÀ CÓ CHUNG ĐẶC ĐIỂM

There are multiple object that can play the soccer, the football, like Messi, MBappe, CR7,.. -> they belong to FOOTBALLER/PLAYER CLASS

BMW, HONDA, TOYOTA,.. -> CAR CLASS 

CLASS: IS A TEMPLATE, A BLUEPRINT(BẢN PHÁC THẢO), A MOLD (CÁI KHUÔN) TO ALLOW US TO GROUP MULTIPLE IDENTICAL OBJECTS

Student class: any guy that is a complex value, has attributes: 
	+ id: _______
	+ name: _______
	+ yob: _______
	+ major: _______
	+ gpa: _______
	+ courses: _______
	…
 CLASS LIKE A FORM, A TEMPLATE TO MODEL ALL THINGS WITH THE IDENTICAL ATTRIBUTE
 A NEW OBJECT, A NEW THING CAN BE CREATED FROM THIS TEMPLATE
				     , A NEW OBJECT CAN BE CLONED FROM THIS TEMPLATE
 CLASS LIKE A MOLD ALSO (CÁI KHUÔN TẠO OBJECT, TẠO BỨC TƯỢNG) TO CREATE OBJECTS

3. OOP STEPS
3.1 RECORNIZE OBJECTS AROUND YOUR PROBLEM/YOUR WORLD, WITH ATTRIBUTES AND ACTIONS
3.2 CLASSIFY/GROUP/CATEGORIZE THE OBJECTS INTO CLASS (A TEMPLATE/ A FORM)
	CREATE CLASS
3.3 CREATE A SPECIAL..

============================================================
						
controller/
	.java
	.java

dto/					entity  entities - a class map directly to table
	.java						ERD
	.java
