Slot8:(According to slot7)

NOTES ON CLASS & OBJECT
- We name everything around us - ta đặt tên cho mọi thứ xung quanh ta
- We name everything around us for easy to communicate with, to talk with
- We name for a simple value and a complex value. A simple value is a value itself, that’s all
And a complex value. A complex value contains inside it multiple attributes or values. There. Is a story when ever we talk about object/complex value

Name means give it a label, a name to call, a name to communicate with
	for easy to refer to it
* SIMPLE VALUE
	PI = 3.14;
	name simple value

	g = 9.8 (gravity - trọng lực)

	VAT = 8%
	total = ???
	c = 300.000km/s (e = m * c^ 2)

* COMPLEX VALUE
Messi =	{ name: Leonardo.., country: Argentina, yob: 1997, goals: ___, number: 10, .. } ==> complex, object
Sky =	{ name: Nguyễn Thanh Tùng.., nick: Sơn Tùng M-TP, yob: 1994, hít: ___ } ==> complex, object

Student s = new Student(“SE1”, “An Nguyễn”, 2003, 8.8); //a certain student/object, name to call this student
	s: object variable
	new Student(…) -> object

* CLASS IS A TEMPLATE, A MOLD, A BLUESPRINT, A FORM WITH MULTIPLE PALCE HODLERS NEED TO BE FILLED IN
	Student:
		ID.      : ___
		NAME: ___
		YOB.  : ___

TO FILL DATA IN TO GET AN OBJECT, A COMPLEX TING WE NEED A FUNNEL/PHỄU TO GET THE OUTSIDE MATERIAL/DATA, AND FILL INSIDE THE FORM/MOLD/THE ATTRIBUTE

The FUNNEL like a method to receive MATERIAL/PARAMETER/OUTSIDE value
			THE FUNNEL IN A CLASS IS A SPECIAL METHOD TO CREATE AN OBJECT, TO CONSTRUCT AN OBJECT
THE FUNNEL CALLED CONSTRUCTOR, GÃ TẠO DỰNG, GÃ XÂY DỰNG NÊN OBJECT

AND WHENEVER YOU HAVE. AN OBJECT, YOU CAN SEE IT, SEE SOME ATTRIBUTE INSIDE -> GET() METHOD - SHOW ME!! TELL ME A LITTLE ABOUT YOURSELF

* WHENEVER YOU WANT TO UPDATE YOUR STATE (TRẠNG THÁI, INFO, THÔNG TIN), LIKE CHANGE THE COVER. CHANGE THE. BACKGROUND, TATOO YOUR SKIN, YOU ARE STILL YOU, NO NEW OBJECT IS CREATED, YOU JUST CHANGE SOME OF YOUR CHARACTER, OBJECT CHARACTER
	-> SET(NEW VALUE PUT IN)
	-> SETTING(NEW VALUE PUT IN)

OBJECT/CLASS MAY HAVE
	-> FUNNEL - CONSTRUCTOR
	-> GET() 
	-> SET() 
	-> OTHER METHOD() OR BEHAVIOUR() TO PROCESS SOMETHING