I. .NET SDK(Software Development Kit)
- A bunch of tools need to install to develop machine to support for development of projects (apply for every programming language)
- .NET SDK  contains: 
	+ .NET tools used by Developer (dev)
	+ RUNTIME environment - tool/program to support for running .NET APP
	+ .NET APP  CAN BE DEVELOPED BY USING C#, CB .NET, C++ .NET, F#

II. ALLOCATE A FOLDER TO STORE YOUR SOURCE CODE
- DO NOT USE VIETNAMESE/UNICODE CHARACTER TO NAME THE FOLDER TO STORE THE CODE (or you will get the error during the compilation of source code). THIS APPLIES FOR ALL OF PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE.
- WRONG: [Kì 5] 
- OK: [KI5], [KI-5], [KI_5]
- OKIE: [SEMESTER5], [SEM-5], SEM_5

HERE IS THE  SUGGESTION FOR STORING THE HANDS-ON SOUCE CODE

Session01-HelloCS
Session02 - Language
Session03 - OOP			(delegate, LINQ - StreamAPI)
..									functional programming 
									Lamda Expression

